

Aysun Mammadli

Date of birth: 16/09/2002 | **Nationality:** Azerbaijani | **Gender:** Female | **Phone number:**

(+994) 0507858479 (Mobile) | Email address: mammadliaysun5@gmail.com | LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/aysun-mammadli-051b311b7

Address: Istanbul street , Apartment 5, AZ 2525, Ganja, Azerbaijan (Home)

ABOUT ME

Teacher / Trainer / Project Manager

With 1.5 years of experience as a teacher, I have gained a comprehensive understanding of the curriculum and its philosophy. I am well-versed in the transdisciplinary approach and have successfully integrated different subject areas to create meaningful and engaging student learning experiences, implementing inquiry-based teaching methods to promote critical thinking, curiosity, and collaboration among the students. I have been working in the field of project management by implementing various social projects for 5 years.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

15/09/2019 - 06/06/2023 Baku, Azerbaijan

FOREIGN LANGUAGE (ENGLISH) TEACHING / GPA 93.4 Azerbaijan University of Languages

Website https://adu.edu.az/

07/2021 - 10/2023

TESOL (TEACHING ENGLISH TO SPEAKERS OF OTHER LANGUAGES) Arizona State University

Website https://globallaunch.asu.edu/teach-english/tesol-certification

WORK EXPERIENCE

18/05/2023 – CURRENT Baku, Azerbaijan

TRAINING FACILITATOR ACT FOR TRANSFORMATION GEMEINNÜTZIGE EG

As Fairtogether Facilitators from South Caucasus countries, we organize workshops for promoting non-violent conflict transformation, communication, diversity, mental health, team building, and conflict resolution. Our activities are organized in the frame of the project "Fairtogether: Stay United for Peace," funded by the German Federal Foreign Office through Ifa, in line with the Zivik programme.

01/10/2022 - 01/08/2023 Baku, Azerbaijan

ENGLISH TEACHER HARVARD EDUCATION CENTRE

- > Planning and delivering engaging English lessons to students of various proficiency levels
- > Developing and implementing instructional materials and strategies to enhance students' language skills.
- > Assessing and evaluating students' progress through assignments, exams, and projects.
- > Providing constructive feedback and guidance to students to help them improve their English language proficiency
- > Maintain a safe and inclusive classroom environment, promoting positive behavior and mutual respect among students.

01/02/2023 - 06/06/2023 Baku, Azerbaijan

TEACHER ASSISTANT SECONDARY SCHOOL NO 7 NAMED AFTER M. RAHIM

- > Assisting the lead English teacher in planning and delivering English lessons to students
- > Supporting students in their language learning journey by providing individual and group tutoring sessions.

- > Grading assignments and exams under the guidance of the lead teacher.
- > Creating and implementing classroom activities and projects.
- > Monitoring students' progress and providing feedback to help them improve their English language skills.
- > Communicating with students' parents or guardians regarding their progress and any concerns

01/06/2021 - 31/08/2021 Baku, Azerbaijan

MANAGER NEED NOW ENGLISH EDUCATION CENTRE

- > Developing and implementing strategies to develop the quality of education.
- > Managing and coordinating the teaching staff, ensuring their professional development and performance.
- > Collaborating with teachers to design and improve curriculum and instructional materials.
- > Monitoring and evaluating students' progress and providing necessary support and interventions.
- > Ensuring the center's facilities and resources are well-maintained and conducive to effective learning.
- > Managing administrative tasks, including scheduling, budgeting, and record-keeping.
- > Establishing and maintaining relationships with parents, addressing their concerns, and providing updates on students' progress.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): AZERBAIJANI

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
TURKISH	C2	C2	C2	C2	C2
ENGLISH	C2	C2	C1	C1	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Teaching | Leadership, Critical thinking and Emotional Intelligence | Organization | Project Management | creativity and problem solving | Communication | skills for training

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

PROJECTS

Project Manager

- > "Equality in Public Life" Grant Project
- > The Outside of World
- > YourSuccess
- > Me in quarantine
- ≻TEDx Sumgait

Participant

- > 4th Solidarity Forum of Volunteers
- > "Winter University of Young Leaders"
- > "One Step" camp
- > New Challenges in Education" form
- > "Mentorship Program," implemented by AUKAA Azerbaijan
- > Erasmus Village by ESN Azerbaijan
- > "Regional Youth Development Program," implemented by US-Educated Azerbaijan Aluminum Association
- > UNICEF Child Protection Core Commitments for Children in Humanitarian Action Playlist

International projects

- > Erasmus + projects
- > "Coach me if you can" (I stage Azerbaijan, II stage Czech Republic)

> "Fairtogether: United for Peace" TOT (Georgia)

SOCIAL AND POLITICAL ACTIVITIES

01/2022 - 06/2023 Coordinator

Community Academy Ensuring community activity among young people in the regions and resolving issues that concern community members in accordance with legal regulations.

06/2022 - 08/2023 Volunteer English teacher

Azerbaijani Youth Public Union I worked as a volunteer English teacher and organized innovative conversation and grammar lessons for low-income and young people who wanted to learn English.

10/2021 - 06/2022 Mentor

Kreshendo Providing individual and group consultations to mentees in personal and career direction, writing blogs, leading social groups, and promoting youth development.

12/2020 – 12/2021 Igv (incoming global volunteer) member

AIESEC Azerbaijan Participation in AIESEC internal training programs, conducting interviews with candidates from abroad who want to volunteer in Azerbaijan, and communicating with foreign AIESEC guests.

12/2021 - 10/2022 Translator

Caucasian Educational Union Translation and printing of sources that are not available in the Azerbaijani language from English to Azerbaijani.

06/2020 - 12/2020 Team Leader

Power of Thought Public Union To lead a Debate club with 35-40 members, to provide debate training for members, to present

and implement a project on behalf of the club to organize a debate tournament.

HONOURS AND AWARDS

"Teacher of the Future" - the Ministry of Science and Education of the Republic of Azerbaijan

Best Debate Speaker medals and certificates - AUL Debat Club

Make the Idea Real 2022" Grant Winner - the Youth Fund of the Republic of Azerbaijan

" Girls Making Changes" Scholarship Winner - Azerbaijan Institute of Education

PUBLICATIONS

"Lexical features of terms in Azerbaijani and English languages" - 2023

Scientific dissertation

"Challenges arise in both conventional and online educational settings for children with autism." – 2020

Thesis

DAUF Planner

Annual planner creator